White Privilege with abs Justin beaver
has just broken a
record and sadly that record is not beli
by Justin Bieber instead he's broken the
record previously held by the Beatles
for having two top three Billboard songs
for the most consecutive weeks Jesus
Christ uh anyway that's his formal wear
that is yeah yeah he's going to a
wedding there uh the old record was 12
weeks but the bebs up to 13 which also
happens to be the age of most of his
fans the remaining Beatles took the news
pretty hard when they heard about
Bieber's accomplishment they said quote
who
but since this kid can do anything now
except girl mustache comedians what's
another record Justin Bieber is going to
break Paulie World softest hands yes
M you just want to get lost in them you
just want to roll around in them Mike
Lawrence most cautionary
tail very good Marcel fting off the most
rollers yeah yeah very good
perfect